EZRA SOWDEN-GUZMAN

INTRO

A user interface is more than a pretty picture. In this age of information, these digital points of contact define how we interact with the world around us. My job is to make these experiences delightful and inviting... and to do it with finesse.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Frontend Engineer

Telos Blockchain Foundation | April 2022 - Current Worked on several open source web3 webapps, including a new Ethereum wallet, wallet.telos.net

- · Created localized UIs for a global user base
- Authored components to handle nuanced, complex data from the blockchain
- · Implemented advanced component styling
- · Defined and enforced best practices for code quality
- Established a coherent design system
- Integrated frontend with EVM smart contracts
- Coordinated with a decentralized, global team

Frontend Engineer

URBN | September 2018 - February 2022

Built Nuuly from the ground up, contributing to all aspects of nuuly.com

- Implemented a full suite of e-commerce functionalities (e.g. account management, catalog, product page, cart, reviews, help & feedback)
- Created a modular UI component library
- Integrated with Contentful to create a custom CMS
- · Employed advanced styling, theming, and CSS-only animation techniques
- Drove accessibility efforts
- · Handled compliance with GDPR and CCPA
- Utilized a robust analytics framework (using GA)

Frontend Engineer

SEI Investments Co. | June 2016 - September 2018 Helped design and build web-based features for the gargantuan SEI Wealth Platform

- · Created designs and prototypes for new pages
- Implemented designs & new features

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science

Computer Science Temple University, Philadelphia, PA May 2016

CONTACT

3 610-999-6006

■ esowdenguzman@gmail.com

Philadelphia, PA 19147

GITHUB

github.com/ezra-sg

LINKEDIN

linkedin.com/in/ezra-sg

WEBSITE

ezra-sg.com

TOOLS & TECHNOLOGIES

- JavaScript (ES6+)
- TypeScript
- HTML5
- CSS3+
- Vue.js
- React
- Sass
- Tailwind
- Bootstrap
- · Git & GitHub
- Jest
- Ethers.io

SKILLS

- Accessibility
- Internationalization
- SEO
- Analytics
- Agile & kanban
- · Technical writing